Guide to the New York University Archives Photograph Collection PHOTO.00001
New York University Archives
- Washington Square Park
  - Subseries H: General Views
    - General Views - People (2 of 3), circa 1980-1989 (Box 216, Folder 2)
      - Man, undated; wsp_gv_9_2_46; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 216, Folder 2, Item 46)
      - Man Posing, undated; wsp_gv_9_2_47; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 216, Folder 2, Item 47)
      - USA Today Newspaper Vending Machine, 1983; wsp_gv_9_2_48; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 (Box 216, Folder 2, Item 48)
      - Man Looking at USA Today Newspaper Vending Machine, 1983; wsp_gv_9_2_49; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 (Box 216, Folder 2, Item 49)
      - People in Washington Square Park, undated; wsp_gv_9_2_50; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 (Box 216, Folder 2, Item 40)
      - Demonstration (Smoke-in), 1983; wsp_gv_9_2_51; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 (Box 216, Folder 2, Item 51)
      - Street Vendors, undated; wsp_gv_9_2_52; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 (Box 216, Folder 2, Item 52)
      - Man Skateboarding, undated; wsp_gv_9_2_53; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 216, Folder 2, Item 53)
      - Snow Sculpture in Astor Place, 1983; wsp_gv_9_2_54; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 2, Item 54)
      - Picnic in Washington Square Park, undated; wsp_gv_9_2_55; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 2, Item 55)
      - Men Playing Chess, 1982; wsp_gv_9_2_56; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 2, Item 56)
      - Performer with Parasol, 1981; wsp_gv_9_2_57; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 2, Item 57)
      - Performer with Parasol, 1981; wsp_gv_9_2_58; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 2, Item 58)
      - People Walking in the Snow, 1984; wsp_gv_9_2_59; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 2, Item 59)
      - Street Performer, undated; wsp_gv_9_2_60; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 2, Item 60)
      - Musicians Performing, 1984; wsp_gv_9_2_61; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 2, Item 61)
      - Israel Independence Day Celebration, undated; wsp_gv_9_2_62; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 2, Item 62)
      - Washington Square Park and Arch Under Construction, circa 1890 - 1899; wsp_gv_9_2_63; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 216, Folder 2, Item 63)
      - Students, undated; wsp_gv_9_2_64; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 216, Folder 2, Item 64)
      - Street Performer and Gesticulating Policeman, undated; wsp_gv_9_2_65; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 216, Folder 2, Item 65)
      - Person Skiing, undated; wsp_gv_9_2_66; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 216, Folder 2, Item 66)
      - Street Vendor, "Buck-a-Lunch", undated; wsp_gv_9_2_67; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 216, Folder 2, Item 67)
      - Crowd, Washington Square Park, undated; wsp_gv_9_2_68; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 216, Folder 2, Item 68)
      - Jogger, undated; wsp_gv_9_2_69; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 216, Folder 2, Item 69)
      - Woman Reading Psychology Textbook, undated; wsp_gv_9_2_70; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 216, Folder 2, Item 70)
      - Student Walking, unknown; wsp_gv_9_2_71; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 216, Folder 2, Item 71)
      - Students Reading, undated; wsp_gv_9_2_72; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 216, Folder 2, Item 72)
      - People in Washington Square Park, undated; wsp_gv_9_2_73; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 216, Folder 2, Item 73)
      - Man Playing Flute, undated; wsp_gv_9_2_74; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 216, Folder 2, Item 74)
      - Woman Writing on Ground With Chalk: "On the Square, Around New York", undated; wsp_gv_9_2_75; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 216, Folder 2, Item 75)
      - Man Reading, 1984; wsp_gv_9_2_76; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 216, Folder 2, Item 76)
      - Women Eating, 1968; wsp_gv_9_2_78; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 216, Folder 2, Item 78)
      - Women and Bicycle, undated; wsp_gv_9_2_77; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 216, Folder 2, Item 77)
    - General Views - People (3 of 3), circa 1980-1989 (Box 216, Folder 3)
      - Musicians Performing, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 1)
      - Violinist Performing, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 2)
      - Musician Performing, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 3)
      - Woman in Bikini, Men in Suits, 1965; wsp_gv_9_3_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 4)
      - Man Playing Frisbee, 1971; wsp_gv_9_3_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 5)
      - People Swimming in Fountain, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 6)
      - Washington Square Park, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 8)
      - Christmas Tree Arriving in Washington Square Park, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 7)
      - Crowd in Washington Square Park (High School Student Demonstration), 1968; wsp_gv_9_3_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 9)
      - Men Playing Chess, Washington Square Park, 1983; wsp_gv_9_3_10; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 10)
      - Musicians and Onlookers, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_11; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 11)
      - Comedian Performing in Park, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_12; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 12)
      - Playground, 1983; wsp_gv_9_3_13; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 13)
      - Snowy Park Benches, circa 1970 - 1979; wsp_gv_9_3_14; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 14)
      - Movie Publicity Stunt: "Trenchcoat Body Count Contest", undated; wsp_gv_9_3_15; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 15)
      - Musicians and Onlookers, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_16; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 16)
      - Street Vendor, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_17; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 17)
      - People Walking, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_18; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 18)
      - Man in Suit, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_19; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 19)
      - People Playing in Fountain, Washington Square Park, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_20; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 20)
      - People Dancing in Washington Square Park, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_21; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 21)
      - Street Performer with Parasol, 1981; wsp_gv_9_3_22; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 22)
      - Man and Garbage Can, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_23; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 23)
      - People, Washington Square Park, 1981; wsp_gv_9_3_24; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 24)
      - Crowd Watching Musician Under Washington Square Arch, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_25; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 25)
      - Street Vendor, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_26; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 26)
      - Ice Cream Vendor, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_27; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 27)
      - Jogger, 1980; wsp_gv_9_3_28; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 28)
      - Clowns Performing, 1981; wsp_gv_9_3_29; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 29)
      - Volleyball Game, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_30; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 30)
      - Street Vendor "GI Joe", undated; wsp_gv_9_3_31; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 31)
      - Joggers, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_32; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 32)
      - People Singing, 1981; wsp_gv_9_3_33; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 33)
      - People Playing Volleyball, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_34; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 34)
      - Sanding Truck in Snow, 1984; wsp_gv_9_3_35; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 35)
      - Jog-a-than promotion, 1980; wsp_gv_9_3_36; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 36)
      - Woman Sketching, 1983; wsp_gv_9_3_37; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 37)
      - Bicyclist Jumping, 1983; wsp_gv_9_3_38; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 38)
      - Musicians Performing and Onlookers at Base of Arch, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_39; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 39)
      - People Eating in Park, 1983; wsp_gv_9_3_40; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 40)
      - Woman Walking in Park, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_41; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 41)
      - Man Juggling, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_42; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 42)
      - Jogger in Jog-a-thon, 1980; wsp_gv_9_3_43; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 43)
      - Jogger during Jog-a-thon, 1980; wsp_gv_9_3_44; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 44)
      - People Juggling, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_45; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 45)
      - People in Park, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_46; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 46)
      - Garibaldi Statue, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_47; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 47)
      - Fountain, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_48; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 48)
      - People Walking in a Row, 1973; wsp_gv_9_3_49; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 49)
      - Reconstruction of Washington Square Park Sign, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_50; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 50)
      - Poles on Perimeter of Park, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_51; black-and-white print (photograph), 7 x 9 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 51)
      - Poles on Perimeter of Park, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_52; black-and-white print (photograph), 7 x 9 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 52)
      - Performer and Camera Crew, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_53; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 53)
      - Man Sleeping, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_54; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 54)
      - Musician, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_55; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 55)
      - Street Vendor, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_56; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 56)
    - Restoration Plan, 1964 (Box 217, Folder 1)
      - Plan: Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1964; wsp_rp_10_1_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 217, Folder 1, Item 1)
      - Aerial Plan of Washington Square Park, undated; wsp_rp_10_1_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 217, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - Statues, 1890-1960 (Box 217, Folder 2)
      - Soldiers Marching Near Garibaldi Statue, 1944; wsp_st_10_2_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 217, Folder 2, Item 1)
      - Garibaldi Statue, undated; wsp_st_10_2_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 217, Folder 2, Item 2)
      - Man Sitting at Base of Garibaldi Statue, 1991; wsp_st_10_2_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 217, Folder 2, Item 3)
      - Snow Sculpture, undated; wsp_st_10_2_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 217, Folder 2, Item 4)
      - Statue of Alexander Lyman Holley, 1905; wsp_st_10_2_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 217, Folder 2, Item 5)
      - Italian Centenary Celebrants at Garibaldi Statue, circa 1956 - 1960; wsp_st_10_2_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 217, Folder 2, Item 6)
      - Crowd Around Garibaldi Statue, 1955; wsp_st_10_2_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 217, Folder 2, Item 7)
      - Garibaldi Statue, undated; wsp_st_10_2_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 217, Folder 2, Item 8)
      - Postcard of Park and Garibaldi Statue, undated; wsp_st_10_2_09; color print (postcard), 4 x 6inches (Box 217, Folder 3, Item 9)
    - Winter Scenes, undated (Box 217, Folder 3)
      contact sheets
    - Exhibit Photos, 1889-1990 (Box 217, Folder 4)
      (8 photos mounted on foam core)
    - Company F - 3202 SCSU ASTU NYU, 1944-03-04 (Flat-file-folder 7 Tray 1)
- Washington Square Area
  This series contains photographs and prints of the Washington Square vicinity.
  - Astor Place Subway, circa 1975-1985 (Box 175, Folder 1)
    - Eighth Street Subway Station, undated; wsa_aps_1_1_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - Astor Subway Station, circa 1975 - 1985; wsa_aps_1_1_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - Subway Car Interior, circa 1975 - 1985; wsa_aps_1_1_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 1, Item 3)
    - Astor Place Subway Station, circa 1980 - 1989; wsa_aps_1_1_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 1, Item 4)
    - Astor Place Subway Station, 1980; wsa_aps_1_1_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 1, Item 5)
    - Astor Place Subway Station, 1980; wsa_aps_1_1_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 1, Item 6)
    - Astor Place Subway Station, circa 1975 - 1985; wsa_aps_1_1_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 1, Item 7)
    - Astor Place Subway Station, circa 1975 - 1985; wsa_aps_1_1_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 1, Item 8)
    - Astor Place Subway Station, circa 1975 - 1985; wsa_aps_1_1_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 1, Item 9)
    - Astor Place Subway Station, circa 1975 - 1985; wsa_aps_1_1_10; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 1, Item 10)
    - Eighth Street Subway Station, 1970; wsa_aps_1_1_11; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 1, Item 11)
    - Eighth Street Subway Station, 1970; wsa_aps_1_1_12; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 1, Item 12)
    - Eighth Street Subway Station, 1970; wsa_aps_1_1_13; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 1, Item 13)
  - 693 Broadway, circa 1965 - 1975 (Box 175, Folder 2)
    - 693 Broadway, circa 1965 - 1975; wsa_1_2_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - 693 Broadway, circa 1965 - 1975; wsa_1_2_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 2, Item 2)
    - 693 Broadway (Detail), circa 1965 - 1975; wsa_1_2_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 2, Item 3)
    - 693 Broadway, wsa_1_2_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 2, Item 4)
    - Coffee Shop, 693 Broadway, wsa_1_2_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 2, Item 5)
    - 693 Broadway, wsa_1_2_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 2, Item 6)
    - 693 Broadway, wsa_1_2_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 2, Item 7)
    - 693 Broadway (Detail), wsa_1_2_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 2, Item 8)
  - Basketball Court - West 4th Street, 1981 (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - Basketball Game, undated; wsa_1_3_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 3, Item 1)
    - Basketball Game, 1981; wsa_1_3_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 3, Item 2)
    - Basketball Game, 1981; wsa_1_3_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 3, Item 3)
    - Basketball Game, 1981; wsa_1_3_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 3, Item 4)
    - Basketball Game, 1981; wsa_1_3_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 3, Item 5)
  - Bleecker Street, 1955-1983 (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - Bleecker Street Cinema, Bleecker Between West Broadway and Thompson, wsa_1_4_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 1)
    - Greenwich Hotel, Bleecker Looking West Toward Sullivan, undated; wsa_1_4_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 2)
    - Yipster Front, 1981; wsa_1_4_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 3)
    - Bleecker Street Between MacDougal and Sullivan, undated; wsa_1_4_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 4)
    - Bleecker Street Cinema Marquee, undated; wsa_1_4_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 5)
    - Bleecker Street Between West Broadway and Thompson, undated; wsa_1_4_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 6)
    - Building, East End of Bleecker Street, undated; wsa_1_4_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 7)
    - Bleecker Street Between MacDougal and Sullivan, undated; wsa_1_4_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 8)
    - Bleecker Street at Sullivan Street, undated; wsa_1_4_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 9)
    - Bleecker Street at Thompson Street, undated; wsa_1_4_10; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 10)
    - Phone Booths, Bleecker Street, 1983; wsa_1_4_11; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 11)
    - Saint Barnabas House, 1983; wsa_1_4_12; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 12)
    - Corner of Bleecker and Mulberry Streets, 1983; wsa_1_4_13; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 13)
    - Bleecker Bob's Records, 1983; wsa_1_4_14; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 14)
    - Cafe Rafio, undated; wsa_1_4_15; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 15)
    - Bleecker Street Between Thompson and West Broadway, undated; wsa_1_4_16; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 16)
    - 175 Bleecker Street, undated; wsa_1_4_17; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 17)
    - Men on Bleecker Street, Looking East Toward Thompson, undated; wsa_1_4_18; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 18)
    - Ganga's Used Clothing Store, Undated; wsa_1_4_19; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 19)
    - Folk City, undated; wsa_1_4_20; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 20)
    - Deli-Box Restaurant, Bleecker Street, undated; wsa_1_4_21; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 21)
    - Bleecker Street Between Greene and Mercer, 1955; wsa_1_4_22; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 22)
    - Looking North Up Thompson Street, undated; wsa_1_4_23; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 23)
    - Bleecker and Sullivan Streets, undated; wsa_1_4_24; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 24)
    - New York Switchboard Peoples Information Center, undated; wsa_1_4_25; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 25)
    - New York Switchboard Peoples Information Center, undated; wsa_1_4_26; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 26)
    - New York Switchboard Peoples Information Center, undated; wsa_1_4_27; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 27)
    - Ambulance, Mercer and Bleecker Streets, undated; wsa_1_4_28; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 28)
    - Saint Baranabas House, Interior, 1983; wsa_1_4_29; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 29)
  - Broadway, circa 1964-1990 (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - 640 Broadway at West 4th Street, wsa_1_5_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 1)
    - 640 Broadway at West 4th Street, undated; wsa_1_5_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 2)
    - Costume Shop Window, undated; wsa_1_5_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 3)
    - Billy Idol Fans Waiting in Line for Tickets, circa 1980 - 1990; wsa_1_5_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 4)
    - Child with Pumpkin Toy, wsa_1_5_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 5)
    - 707 Broadway, 1964; wsa_1_5_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 6)
    - Crowd Outside of Tower Records, 1984; wsa_1_5_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 7)
    - Tower Records, 1983; wsa_1_5_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 8)
    - 657 Broadway, 1981; wsa_1_5_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 9)
    - 561 Broadway, 1979; wsa_1_5_10; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 10)
    - 561 Broadway, 1979; wsa_1_5_11; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 11)
    - Building with Scaffolding, undated; wsa_1_5_12; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 12)
    - Church, undated; wsa_1_5_13; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 13)
    - People Waiting in Line Outside of Tower Records, undated; wsa_1_5_14; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 14)